it was that darn kitten again. All this is enabled because we were able to find a way to translate a very hard problem to something our brains do very naturally. So what does this mean? Well, for kittens, it means no more hiding in ones and zeros. For me, it means no more wasted weekends. For cyber, it means we have a radical new way to tackle the most impossible problems. It means we have a new weapon in the evolving theater of cyber warfare, but for all of us, it means that cyber engineers now have the ability to become first responders in emergency situations. When seconds count, we've unlocked the means to stop the bad guys. Thank you. (Applause)
era ese gatito otra vez. Todo esto fue posible gracias a que pudimos encontrar la forma de traducir un problema muy difícil en algo que nuestros cerebros hacen con mucha naturalidad. ¿Qué quiere decir esto? Bueno, para los gatitos significa ya no esconderse entre los unos y ceros. Para mí, significa ya no desperdiciar más fines de semana. Para la ciberseguridad significa que tenemos una nueva forma radical de abordar los problemas imposibles. Significa que tenemos una nueva arma en el teatro cambiante de la ciberguerra, pero para todos, significa que los ciberingenieros ahora pueden ser los primeros en responder en situaciones de emergencia. Cuando los segundos cuentan, hemos desatado los medios para detener a los malos. Gracias. (Aplausos)